{
    "subject": "resource/Mad_Love_(1995_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/producer",
    "object": "resource/David_Manson_(producer)",
    "human_readable": "The producer of the film 'Mad Love' (1995) is David Manson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9154338240623474,
            "question": "What is the title of the film produced by David Manson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9048017859458923,
            "question": "Is David Manson known for producing other films besides 'Mad Love'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.884722888469696,
            "question": "Who produced the film 'Mad Love'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7926961779594421,
            "question": "What is the name of the producer of 'Mad Love'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6800239086151123,
            "question": "Can you name any other films produced by David Manson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5522271990776062,
            "question": "What year was the film 'Mad Love' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48796385526657104,
            "question": "Who acted in the film 'Mad Love'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44656816124916077,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Mad Love'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3204371929168701,
            "question": "Where was the film 'Mad Love' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2161588817834854,
            "question": "What are some themes explored in 'Mad Love'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The producer of the film 'Mad Love' (1995) is David Manson.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5969_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was the film 'Mad Love' filmed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5969_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film 'Mad Love'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5969_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who acted in the film 'Mad Love'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5969_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5969_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5969_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5969_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5969_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5969_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5969_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5969_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5969_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5969_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5969_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that David Manson produced the film \"Mad Love\" (1995), which aligns with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}